Thank you for watching!
by H.
The end. Thank you for watching.
Shall we go to practice now?
I would like to go.
You've been waiting for me.
I have to go. Let's hurry up and go.
Let's go!
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
I'll be teaching today.
My name is Sho Aranami, an alumnus of Yokohama Daisy Dancers.
Basically, I'm an outfielder, and I used to play in the outfield,
I was playing in the shadows today,
I will try to teach you well and carefully.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
This distance is probably,
Maybe because, for example, there is more space behind us,
It feels further away,
But basically, that's the distance.
What's that?
Here,
This is what baseball players do all the time.
Throwing,
Ohtani can throw it 160 meters wide,
A player who can hit at this distance.
If he could get a strike from the top of the first at worst,
I think it would be cool.
So, even if he bowed at first,
I think it would be great.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I think I can start throwing now,
I'll just keep going,As it is, properly,
In this moment of plaise,
Keep your toes pointed to the touch,
First of all, keep your navel firmly to the side.
Here we go.
That's good.
And from there, you're going to throw it like this,
Like this.
Like this,
Hold it like this.
It's good.
Very good.
Thank you very much.
Oh, it works.
It's good.
Let's go.
OK!
You can all raise it hard like this now, and you can still throw.
and you can still throw like this.
If you throw like this, your body will rotate a lot, and it's hard to do.
So, when your toes are pointing firmly in the direction you want to throw
Raise your toes forward like this.
I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to batmint now.
I'm going to play batmint now.
Eeeee!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've been working on the basics of this.
Today, I think everyone's arms are going to be doing batmint like this...
Well, not tennis, but...
I play volleyball.Playing Volleyball
When you attack in volleyball
You have to attack like this.
You have to attack with a slap.
When you throw the ball now, if you turn like this...
Or throw like this.
I can't use my arms as big as they used to be.
If you go up like a ballet...
Ohhh!
Throw the ball up firmly.
This arm swing is very important.
I'm going to try a little bit of this.
Okay.
I'm going to throw it around here.
Throw it as high as you can.
It doesn't matter where you go.
Here we go.
Yes, from higher and higher up. It'll go straight down, so it'll bounce straight down.
Yes, from the top.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, but more like this back waist use, like this back waist use, like this back waist use, like this back waist use.
If you hold the heavy weight on your back like this...
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice!
Here we go.
He was hitting everything.
I'm scared.
Here we go.
Yes, good, good.
That's really good. That's stronger.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
That's great.That's great.
Oh, that's nice.
Up, up.
Oh, my God.
That was fast.
Okay, okay, okay!
And now, when you've definitely done it, come to this side.
And you're going to put your weight on your front foot
on your front foot like this.
on the front foot here like this.
It's very important when you throw.
I think you'll be stronger if you ride forward firmly from here.
I see.
That's good.
Then the weight goes really far forward.
All the way to here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, I was just saying, the racket... we've got to split the racket here.
It went here.
Yeah! That's it!
Let's go for it!
When you piece the ball.
Put your thumb under it like this.
Now, when you piece this, put your thumb under it like this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's good.
And that's how you grip it.
And if you had a grip, I think it would make it easier to throw even with three pieces.
I'm going to do that now.
This one's a little bit lighter, so just that one.
So that's the image I just showed you.
I'm going to put my arms around myself first, and put my feet on the ground.
And then, with your navel...So, with the belly button.
Oh, that's nice.
fast!
First, you run from here.
Yeah, and then the belly button.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Ho!
Oh, yeah! But your hands will be smaller, so you'll have to put your hands...
Yes!
I'm gonna start turning my hand a little bit here.
Ho!
Oh! That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good!
That's great!
That's good!
Oh, man!
They're retrieving it.
Oh!
Oh! That's what I'm talking about!
That's good!
Amazing!
Thank you!
First of all, I have to learn to throw properly and far.
Oh!
Yes! That's good!
And no longer!
Amazing!
This is probably a real throw!
It's heavy! It's heavier than before.
Oh!
I think I can probably throw it now.
I can do it!
That's great!Amazing!
Fast! So far so good!
Good, good, good!
Oh! That's good, that's good, that's good.
What? I don't know what to do.
Here we go.
Oh! Is this thing coming? Oh, my God.
Okay, let's start with the blue one.
Blue! Blue!
Oh, my God!
Blue!
Oh, my God, it looks like him!
I love it!
Oh, my God!
Wow! That's fast!
That's great!
Ha!
Great, great!
Nice, nice, nice.
Nice, now.
Huh? Huh? Huh? No, no, no.
Oh, yeah.
But I don't think you know what you just did.
Fasher action.
ok, let's put it in.
Oh, you want to do it here?
Would you rather try it once?
How much?
Oh, I don't know how much to do.
A little more than that.
Maybe if I aim for that glove...
I'm thinking about the top of the net.
Aim for the end of the blue line.
Okay, here we go.Here we go.
I can reach your eyes, too. That's great.
And I'll take care of the controls now.
Up first.
Yes, yes, yes, OK, that's good.
Forward.
That's good.
I think that's totally fine.
Oh! I bought a mask!
Go, go, go, go!
Yes!
Please!
All right!
I'm sweating so much.
It's amazing.
I think it's cooler if I go out for a bit.
It's fun.
I'm gonna wear it in about three hours.
I'm so sweaty.
Oh, my gosh.
You're gonna want to throw a lot of balls.
Is that okay?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let's take a step forward.
Se-ne-tee!
Excuse me.
That's great.
Let's bow.
I want the three of us to do our best!
I want to do my best!
I just want to work hard!
Ask the rest of the members for their feelings too.
With everyone's feelings on our shouldersWith everyone's feelings on their shoulders.
Sometimes you bury them.
I don't know, it's just... when you're standing there...
If it was in good shape, I'd say it's about right.
It's like a dream.
The mound is right in the middle of this one.
And the base is right there, in the middle of the sheet.
You want to pace yourself?
Yes, sir!
Go for it!
You're really fast.
Oh!
That's good for first place today.
Yay!
That was so good!
Now...
Now we have a real leader.
Oh, but that one might be more awesome!
So far, no more one-punching like a gorilla...
It's hard, it's hard.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm just gonna let my hands go.
I'm gonna get this thing started. I'm just gonna do my best.
I want to do my best.
You're progressing very quickly.
Really?
You've been teaching me so much.
It's like, "Oh, that's how it's supposed to be.
I mean, the process...
He didn't explain in detail how it happened.
If I had learned the joy of throwing a baseball when I was 5 years old.
I might have played baseball all my life.
Did you really give me that?Did you really give me that?
Yeah, it's up there.
I'll give you three or three.
It's a little early to open it again.
Look, look, look, it's kind of following you right up to the front.
It's all lit up.
Oh, but it's really...
It's amazing.
Asahi is counting on you.
I'll do my best.
Please do it a lot!
Strikes... strikes... strikeouts...
If it's three strikes, you're out of baseball.
Strike one, strike two, strike three.
But you might as well enjoy it.
You don't get to stand on a mound like this very often.
I don't think you get to stand on a mound like this very often.
If the person on stage was in the opposite position...
I'm sure we'd be nervous too.
It's normal to be nervous about something you're not used to.
Enjoy it.
We've practiced so much.
I'll just let the result be the result.
Maybe we'll have another chance to do it the next time.
You might get another chance to do it.
First of all, believe in what you've practiced.
Then you just have to throw yourself at it.
I think that's important.
Yes, sir.
OK.
Thank you very much.
That's great!
That's great! My first time here!Amazing!!! My first time there!
Oh, my God!
Great!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
That's great!
He said it's okay to win again and change,
Maybe the most important thing is to be heard.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Wow, but I notice a little.
It's something, but it's going to work and not work in some rounds.
I'm nervous.
Calm down a little bit.
I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know. Let's hold hands.
Wow.
Our hearts go out to this third class!
Go for it!
That was important!
Yes!
It was perfect!
But it's going to be fun!
She's from Kanagawa Prefecture, and I'm honored!
It's true!
It's going to be a big, big day.
Yeah!
I'll be cheering for all the athletes.Cheer for the athletes!
Good luck everyone! And have fun cheering for the athletes!
With that in mind
I'm going to throw the ball!
A smile is better than a determined face
Fujiko
I'm nervous, but I don't know how many people will be there.
I was only seeing the catcher at the practice, but I think there are many people in front of me.
But when I think of all the people in front of me, I don't know where to look.
I don't know where to look.
I'll do my best.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are the Factory of Motto.
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
Today, the one who welcomes you with everyone on stage,
Or perhaps you would like to join us with all of you.
Let me welcome you with everyone in support
I would be happy if you could join us and make it a great day for us.
I would be very happy if you could join us.
Thank you very much.
So, starting today, the middle of the 2000 Blue Luck Shoes selection will be,
Once, we will have you perform a miraculous performance match.
The person who will appear today is a representative of the Not Equal Key members,
Goro Yanosawa, a native of Kanagawa Prefecture,
Goro Yanosawa.
Moto Sakurai.
Oooh!
And now, chosen by Anrakuji among the members,
Shiori Nakata from Fukushima Prefecture.
Let's start with Ms. Shiori Nakata.
Let's go to the beach!
Yay!
Manmaru!Manmaru!
Good night!
Thank you for your hard work.
Surprise!
Please.
Anpanman Slider
20 years
Oh!
Congratulations.
Next Slider
FINISH
Happy New Year's Eve!
Thank you very much.
Let's all dance!
Let's dance together!
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
How did you feel about your back?
I was really nervous because it was a very short moment.
But we were able to practice a lot together,
It was a very valuable experience for me,
It was also a very precious experience for me to have blue gloves on my hands,
Thank you very much.
I couldn't believe that I would be pitching at Yokohama Stadium,
But when I came out of the stadium, everyone waved to me,
It was so warm and made me want to do my best.
It was a very enjoyable time.
Thank you very much.
From the moment the doors of Yokohama Stadium opened, there were so many people in the audience,
The music of the sea that was coming on board was playing,
We were allowed to appear,
I felt like it was something that was really real, but so good that it didn't feel real.I felt like it was something that was really real, but so nice that it didn't feel real.
With this glove with VSTAR's logo on it, and this ball with today's date on it,
and this ball with today's date on it,
I am so thankful for the opportunity to pitch at the Ceremonial Pitch,
I am very grateful for this precious experience,
I still have to work on my shoulder,
I still have to work on my shoulder and train more for the next time,
Next time, I would like to pitch for the 12th consecutive time,
I hope to be a group with strong shoulders so that I can pitch 12th place consecutively next time,
I would like to thank all the Berryz KOBO fans and everyone who came to this stadium,
I really got a lot of power from Berryz KOBO fans and everyone who came to the stadium,
I will do my best to warm up the venue after the show.